For this exercise, as we've just shown, we've gone ahead and set up a restaurant status list
as the single source of truth. So we can see here with the type right, we have the import type
status list. And here we're using that funky little syntax where we have type of restaurant
status list and the number. And so for this particular exercise, what I want you to do is
basically mirror what we did with diet list where we can maintain that as a single source of truth
rather than having that duplicated across types and constants.
All right, hopefully that was pretty straightforward, minus the awkward syntax. But let's go ahead
and do that together, shall we? Let me check out the branch for 06 finish. So the first thing
we're going to do is we're going to go ahead and make sure that this is type cast as a cons.
Because otherwise, basically, type trip cannot read those values. And so what we'll, I didn't
get to capture on the last, right before we do one of the exercise, is that VS Code was actually
yelling at me because when I imported restaurant lists, I did not tell it it was a type.
So some of you might have seen that. So once you add that type here, that should resolve
the issues at hand. But this is one of the reasons why we actually need to do this as a constipet
because otherwise without it, it's kind of like, it's an array of strings. So this is what allows
us to read it, the way it is. But anyhow, okay, so we have that. And then we have our diet list.
And then once we save that, we'll come in here. And once again, it's type of diet list. And then
it's accessing the array, how via numbers because an array is index via numbers. So that's
how you can try to remember it. But yeah, it's hopefully the type trip API comes out with an
easier way for us to do this going forward.